You look fine.
元気そうだね
I'm fine.
元気です
That's a nice view.
良い眺めですね
Undercolor.
下色
Can I apply a little bit of the underlying color?
その下色を ちょっとずつ塗ってもいい?
Is it ok to paint it?
塗 って も いい?
Can I paint it?
塗ってもいい?
Let's try reducing it.
縮小してみようか
I've never done it.
やったことない
What sport did you play?
何のスポーツしたの?
There's no reason at all.
全然わけがない
You seem to be feeling well today.
今日は体調良さそうだね
You look fine.
元気そうだね
I'm fine.
元気です
I feel like I slept well.
よく眠れたっぽい感じですね
It suits you.
似合いますね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It suits you.
似合いますよね
Very good.
すごく良い
Take it.
持ってみて
It's running, isn't it?
走ってるよね
That's a nice view.
良い眺めですね
That's right.
そうだよね
It's too obvious.
ついっきりすぎて
I've been feeling the urge to turn on some news.
ちょっとニュースかけたくなってきたんですけど
Is it no good?
ダメですか?
It's Rion, Rion.
リオンです、リオン
To.
に
It can be done.
でき るんですね
Are you watching too much?
見すぎですか?
ratio.
比率
Would you like me to take it off for a while?
ちょっと脱いでほしいかな
underwear.
下着
Take off your clothes.
服を脱いで
Can I wait?
待っていい?
Yukku
ゆっく
Rito.
り と
underwear.
下着
Just look over here.
ちょっとこっち向いて
That underwear is a nice color.
良い色だね、その下着
Can I take off your underwear little by little?
その下着を ちょっとずつ脱いでもいい?
Is it cold?
寒いですか?
You have such a beautiful face
すごい綺麗な顔して
I see.
る ね
Have you been training lately?
最近、鍛えてますか?
Sports?
スポーツ?
I haven't trained.
鍛えてはない
I see.
そうか
It would be nice if it was in the back.
後ろだったらいいよね
Let's take a look at the back.
後ろちょっと見てみようかな
Private underwear.
プライベートの下着です
I've never done it.
やったことない
Maybe I just don't remember.
記憶にないだけかもしれない
Can I take you to the front?
前に連れて行ってもらっていい?
Shall I put it in?
入れちゃおうか
That's fine.
それでいいよ
If it's behind
後ろだったら
good?
いい?
Can I open it for you?
開 けてもらっていい?
Should I put it in?
入れちゃおうかな
shower
シャワ
- But I didn't like being cute.
ー でも可愛いの嫌だったね
The head of my underwear is on.
下着の頭ついてる